elliottwave.com 2018-09-07

# Privacy Policy :: Elliott Wave International

Elliott Wave International (EWI) wants to provide you with a rewarding, informative and exciting visit to sites in the Elliott Wave Network as well as safeguard your privacy online. This privacy statement covers the websites of ElliottWave.com, Deflation.com and eWaves.com and is effective as of 7/24/2015. 

**_DATA COLLECTION POLICY_**

_**Collection of Information**_

**Aggregate Data:** You may visit web pages within the Elliott Wave Network of websites referenced above without giving us any personally identifiable information (PII) about yourself. We do collect aggregate (non-PII) data such as browser type, connection speed, previously viewed products on our site, click paths, etc. about users using cookies (See the "Tracking Cookies" section below). Any data we obtain automatically using these tracking technologies is used to enhance the website experience such as exposing visitors to other relevant services that we feel could be complementary. We also use this data for analytic trend studies. You will be notified when your personally identifiable information is collected by any third party that is not our agent/service provider, so you can make an informed choice as to whether or not to share your information with that party. We do not link aggregate user data with personally identifiable information.

**Personally Identifiable Information:** In order to deliver services you've requested and personalize your experience with the Elliott Wave Network of websites referenced above further, we may ask for you to give personally identifiable information (PII ) such as your name, postal address, email address, phone number, interests or preferences, IP address, credit card number, etc. We are committed to protecting all of the personally identifiable information that we collect and thus this information is kept strictly confidential and is not distributed to third parties who are not service providers or as described in this privacy statement without your consent.

We store the information that we collect through cookies and clear gif images to create a "profile" of your preferences. We then tie your personally identifiable information (such as your name, email address, and interests or preferences), and your purchasing history, to information in your customer profile, in order to provide tailored promotions and marketing offers and to enhance your website experience. 

We may request personally identifiable information when you:

  * Sign up for one of our free content programs such as Club EWI, Free Email Newsletters, or our Affiliate Program
  * Purchase something through our online store or friendly customer service representatives
  * Participate in a survey, whether through an email or on any of the Elliott Wave Network of websites referenced above 
  * Access password-protected resources hosted on any of the Elliott Wave Network of websites referenced above
  * Open an email or click a link within our email communications

**Testimonials:** Likewise, if you choose to submit a testimonial on the Elliott Wave Network of websites referenced above (Members and Affiliates areas), we will ask for your permission to share it with our other customers. You also have the option to post anonymous testimonials. You may also request that a testimonial be removed from the Elliott Wave Network of websites referenced above by contacting EWI Customer Care.

**_Our Promise to You_**

We value you as a customer of EWI and likewise we value your privacy. The information we collect is kept strictly confidential and will not be given, sold, or shared with outside companies who are not service providers or as described in this privacy statement. 

EWI does not distribute unsolicited bulk advertising via email (spam). You may opt-out of any of our various email lists, such as our Free Email Newsletters, Club EWI, Subscriber Updates, etc. by simply following the instructions included in each email communication, by visiting the My Account section of ElliottWave.com, or by contacting EWI Customer Care. 

In order to comply with the Federal CAN-SPAM Act of 2003, we may provide a list of email addresses of customers who have opted-out of EWI's email lists to other companies that send email on our behalf (Email Service Providers). This suppression list is used solely for the purpose of preventing an unsubscribed EWI customer from receiving EWI-related emails from another company. We require all companies that send to their email lists on our behalf to sign an agreement prohibiting the suppression list from being used for any other purpose than not sending you our email. We conform to all state and federal laws regarding this issue. 

_**Use of Collected Information**_

Any of the information we collect from you whether PII or aggregate may be used in any or all of the following ways: 

  * To supply you with the resource(s), service(s), product(s), or subscription(s) you've requested/ordered
  * To personalize your experience both on the Elliott Wave Network of websites referenced above and in our email to better respond to your individual interests and preferences 
  * To improve the Elliott Wave Network of websites' offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you 
  * To more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs 
  * To send periodic emails 
    * The email address you provide for order processing or sign up will be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information that we feel may be of interest to you. 

We may also disclose your personally identifiable information: 

  * As required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process 
  * When we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request 
  * To third party service providers to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personally identifiable information _only as necessary_ to provide such services
  * If EWI is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website of any change in ownership or uses of your personally identifiable information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personally identifiable information

**_Tracking Cookies_**

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies on the Elliott Wave Network of websites referenced above. We do link the information we store in cookies to personally identifiable information. 

We use session cookies, which expire when you close your browser, to make it easier for you to navigate our site. We use persistent cookies to track and target your interests to enhance your experience on the Elliott Wave Network of websites referenced above as well as give credit to our affiliate sites for orders placed through the Elliott Wave Network of websites referenced above. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time but you can remove them by clearing your browser's history/temporary internet files. 

If you reject cookies, you may still use the Elliott Wave Network of websites referenced above, but your ability to use some areas of our sites, such as contests or surveys, will be limited. 

Some of our business partners (e.g., tracking utility companies, video delivery services) use cookies (clear gif images a.k.a. Web Beacons) on our sites. We have no access to or control over these cookies nor do we tie the information gathered to your personally identifiable information. To change your video cookie preferences, please follow this [link](http://www.adobe.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html).

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by the Elliott Wave Network of websites referenced above only and does not cover the use of cookies by any other third parties. 

_**Behavioral Targeting / Re-targeting**_

We partner with a third party ad network to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partner uses cookies and Web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other Web sites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may [opt-out](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/). Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads. 

**_Links to Other Sites_**

The Elliott Wave Network of websites referenced above contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Elliott Wave International. Please be aware that we, Elliott Wave International, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. 

We encourage you to be aware when you leave one of our sites and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. 

This privacy statement applies only to information collected by Elliott Wave International through the Elliott Wave Network of websites referenced above and email communications. 

_**Social Media Widgets**_

The Elliott Wave Network of websites include Social Media Features, such as Facebook widgets, Twitter widgets or interactive mini-programs, that run on our sites. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing the feature. 

**_Email to a Friend_ **

The Elliott Wave Network of webisites includes a "Email to a Friend" Feature. This Feature is hosted by a third party and is governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. A link to their privacy policy is provided on the feature. 

**_Access to Personally Identifiable Information_**

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our services, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate your account by emailing, calling or writing our customer service department at the contact information listed below. You may also access some of your information to correct, delete, or update it by going to the My Account section of ElliottWave.com. We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us by phone, mail, or email at the contact information listed below. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

**_Security_**

The security of your personally identifiable information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as your credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). 

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personally identifiable information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personally identifiable information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

If you have any questions about security on the Elliott Wave Network of websites referenced above, you may contact us via the contact information listed below.

_**EMAIL COMMUNICATION POLICY**_

**_Email Communications from the Site_**

In addition to the services mentioned above, there are numerous sections of the Elliott Wave Network of websites referenced above where visitors may request that content pieces and email communications be sent to them via email. EWI intends that any of the notification programs (Free Email Newsletters, Club EWI, Subscription Alerts, Free Trial, etc.) do not result in undesired email to members. The email address you provide for order processing or sign up will be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your requested content, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information that we feel may be of interest to you. 

Visitors to the Elliott Wave Network of websites referenced above may choose to become an EWI Affiliate. As part of our affiliate program, we will inform you of new content that is available for your website. You may cancel your affiliation with EWI at any time as well as opt-out of these communications by following the instructions within each email communication. 

_**Choice/Opt-out**_

We provide you the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes, when we ask for this information. 

If you no longer wish to receive our email newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each email newsletter or communication. You may also opt-out of certain communications under the My Account section of ElliottWave.com, or you may contact us by phone, mail, or email at the contact information listed below. 

You will be notified when your personally identifiable information is collected by any third party that is not our agent/service provider, so you can make an informed choice as to whether or not to share your information with that party.

_**FUTURE CHANGE NOTICE**_

**_Changes in this Privacy Statement_**

If we decide to change our privacy statement, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home pages of the Elliott Wave Network of websites referenced above, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on the home pages of the Elliott Wave Network of websites referenced above prior to the changes becoming effective. 

_**CONTACT INFORMATION**_

_Mailing Address_

Elliott Wave International  
P. O. BOX 1618  
Gainesville, Georgia 30503  
USA 

_Phone_

800-336-1618 or 770-536-0309

_Email_

customercare@elliottwave.com
